Henry Claude Bernardin

347.236.5657 Cell Henry.Bernardin@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a committed professional with over five years of managerial and administrative experience, and a year of front-end software development experience, seeking to assume a role which will facilitate continued personal and professional growth. I enjoy working with others to achieve an objective on time and with excellence.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front-End Software Developer & Designer

New York, NY-2019-Present

- Communicate with clients to deliver quality software projects and follow up to ensure that the customer is satisfied with product
- Develop custom front-end HTML, CSS, & JavaScript websites
- Configure domain names and hosting through Netlify.com

Program Manager, Cerebral Palsy Associations of New York State New York, NY—2016-Present

- Responsible for ensuring compliance with all state and federally mandated requirements pertaining to the program (OMRDD, OSHA, COA, Medicaid, etc.)
- Documentation, review and submission of all financial accounts, ledgers associated with personal allowance, earned income and members in house ledgers for cash on hand, including staff payroll, and site expenditures
- Ensure the proper reporting, investigation and review of all incidents relative to OPWDD Part 624 regulations and the Justice Center

Assistant Program Manager, Catholic Charities Neighborhood Services

Brooklyn, NY -2014-2016

- Supervised and ensured completion of apartment inspections and fire drills; ensured the safety, maintenance and upkeep of the building and apartments through ongoing assessment of maintenance requirements and communication with the Engineering Department regarding repair needs of individual apartments and common areas
- Provided support in order to ensure constant audit readiness and regulatory compliance of all records, services, and maintenance issues
- Responsible for assisting in training of all policies, procedures in accordance with OPwDD regulations and guidelines

EDUCATION

City University of New York- Brooklyn College

B.S., Double Major in Health Nutrition Sciences & Psychology — 2006-2010

SKILLS SUMMARY

Languages/Computer/Administrative

Haitian Creole (fluent), Spanish (intermediate), HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Sass, Responsive Design, Testing/Debugging, UI Design, Git/GitHub, Bootstrap, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Adobe Photoshop (intermediate), Microsoft Word, Outlook (advanced)

REFERENCES

Available upon request.